< front-end developer />

I am a self-taught front-end developer. I gained my first experience on this position at the companies Webiso and Asco, where I successfully implemented the projects I was in charge of. Working for the Sabre Corporation and creating applications for the airline industry allowed me to combine the tourism sector knowledge with the acquired programming skills. Currently, I pay most attention to React.js and I would like to develop in this field. What brings me the most satisfaction at work is constant challenge, opportunity to develop myself and learning new things. My Experience and soft skills acquired at jobs beyond IT branch certainly bring many positive aspects to the team I join. I am open to cooperation on B2B contract or employment contract.



(**) +48 503 58 34 37

tomasz.rysak@o2.pl

github.com/tomi5

in linkedin.com/in/tomasz-rysak

Skawina, woj. małopolskie

Technologies I use:

- JavaScript
- · React.js, Vue.js, Next.js
- · Redux, Vuex
- TypeScript
- HTML 5
- CSS3 (flexbox, grid, BEM), Sass
- Bootstrap 4
- Git

SKILLS

- Jest, Enzyme, Playwright, TestCafe, Cypress.jo
- Knockout.js
- Jenkins, TeamCity
- GraphQL basics
- PHP (SMARTY), C#, Python basics

Others Abilities:

- fluent in CorelDraw
- basic in Visual Basis and fluent in Excel
- Photoshop (PSD slicing and basic image processing)

· English - upper intermediate

• Polish - native speaker

- traveling, extreme and qualified tourism
- · low cost flight search
- nature photography
- sports: football, muay-thai, cycling, snowboarding
- · travel books and magazines
- stock exchange

SELECTED PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2021.09 - ongoing Sii Poland - Software engineer - B2B

- working as a contractor for Sabre Cooperation, including:
- · developing web application for the airline industry (Digital Workspace),
- · developing payment gateway (SEPG Hosted Payment Page),
- developing PWA multi-tenant e-commerce PWA intended for the aviation industry. The platform allows to create and manage flight reservations (EzyCommerce),
- code testing: unit and e2e
- technologies: React.js, Vue.js, Next.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, Redux, Vuex, Jest, Enzyme, TestCafe, Cypress.jo, Playwright, GraphQL, CSS/Sass, Git, Jenkins, TeamCity, C#.

2020.11 - 2021.09 Asco Systemy Informatyczne - Front-End Developer - B2B

- creating websites with HTML (CSHTML), CSS (SASS, Bootstrap), JavaScript (Knockout.js),
- maintaining and improving existing websites,
- improving a proprietary CMS
- analyzing and implementing customer requirements.

2019.12 - 2020.05 Webiso - Front-End Developer - B2B

- creating websites with HTML, CSS (SASS, Bootstrap), JavaScript and PHP,
- CMS implementations,
- writing and implementing CMS Plugins (PHP, Smarty),
- maintaining and improving websites,
- getting feedback from users and customers.

2016.03 - 2019.11 Orlando Travel - travel specialist

- · creating an own offer of group tours and supervising ongoing tours,
- customer acquisition and maintaining good customer relationship,
- acquiring and contacting contractors (mainly in English),
- the originator of the offer of own tourist trips with Dynamic Packing implementation and supervision,
- · website update using CMS.

2013.08 - 2016.03 Strefa Wypraw - travel specialist

- creating tailor-made trips,
- supervising ongoing tours organized by the Tour Organizator,
- contact with the customers and contractors,

OWN PROJECTS

Visited Countries Map

Used: React.js, TypeScript, Styled-components, RestAPI

Personal CV

Used: React.js, Styled-components

LandLab - commercial project for landscape architecture company Used: HTML5, CSS3, JS, CMS MADE SIMPLE, SMARTY

EDUCATION

2007 - 2012 - Jagiellonian University in Krakow

Master's degree in Geography, specialisation in Tourism





I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

-ANGUAGES